One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
Monster
Showing mercy is unbecoming of a raging lion!
Ouch!
Taking the second rumble ball is like gambling.
There are seven transformations in total.
In other words, the probability of
getting Arm Point is one in seven.
If I could get it, I could hammer
my strongest attack into him.
That's my only chance!
Arm Point!
Shishi Kebab!
For my friends...
Arm Point!
Wrong one!
Wrong one! Why doesn't it come out?!
My body is at the end of its rope.
I somehow have to get Arm Point out!
Hm?
Whoa!
It's out! I didn't notice it!
Be prepared!
I'll put everything I have...
into this attack!
Cloven...
Shishi Finger Pistol!
If I back off now, I won't get another chance!
Cloven...
Iron Body: Adamantine!
Roseo Blizzard!
Go down!
That was my best attack!
Ahh...
Ahh... splendid...!
It was indeed a beautiful blizzard of...
cherry blossom petals.
I can't...
Did I do it?
I can't bear it anymore!
I will give you hell!
Tempest Kick: Lotus!
This is it. I no longer have the energy to fight back.
Chopper!
Chopper, what in the world did you do?
I don't remember.
"I don't remember" doesn't cut it.
It was good that no one died, at least.
Even while you were sleeping,
the entire country was making
a big fuss about that night.
How are we going to settle that?
So I did something that terrible?
You almost destroyed an entire village.
It's fine that you love experiments,
just like your old man did,
but you have to account for all possible outcomes when conducting them.
All possible outcomes?
Good grief. You even stir up trouble like him.
I'm sorry, Doctorine.
I won't do it again.
I'll never do it again,
so please don't kick me out.
You're such a fool. Hurry up and get better.
I can't even go shopping.
Vital Response!
Hair Bind!
Don't cry. Don't cry.
If you do, it'll be a disgrace to your manhood.
He's gonna kill me.
This isn't an evening in a mountain
village where you can hear the cicadas.
This is a journey to hell's furnace
that you knew could come.
The leaves I took from a willow tree to give to you as a parting gift,
hoping for your return someday,
are colored crimson!
Take it! Now, now, now, now!
Crimson... Song of the Willow!
I'm gonna die.
Robin! That's right. I can't give up!
He slipped away from my Hair Bind!
Rumble!
If I'm gonna die anyway, I'll do it!
Just please, nobody come into this room.
I used three rumble balls.
Then I lost consciousness and after that...
You could say that your devil fruit
powers went out of control.
Don't ever go down that path again, okay?
It's too much power. It destroys
foes, friends, and even your own body.
What you turned into was just like a real...
monster.
Dammit!
I'm super this week, and yet I still
had a harder time than I thought.
But, well...
I got his key.
No. 4.
The key the swordsman and
the nose wanted was No. 2, right?
This guy had No. 4.
That guy had No. 3.
And there's only one left.
The one with the No. 2 key
is that secretary woman!
I'd better hurry up.
I'll go help them out!
You guys don't have much time, right?
I thought you weren't going to go easy on me.
Did I hear you wrong?
How dare you mock me?!
I won't let you get away with it!
Then, bring it on.
You don't have to wait. The battle
has already started, you know.
I'm surprised that an ability user
would take a bath in front of her enemy.
If your body is halfway submerged,
you shouldn't have full use of your powers.
Are you saying that I'm
leaving myself wide open?
You don't have to worry about it,
because just like me, you can't
exert your strength, either.
Pardon me for a bit.
What'd you do to me?!
Isn't solving a mystery like that one of
the true joys of fighting an ability user?
It was definitely this woman
who put Sanji-kun in that state.
I have to be careful. Or there's no
point in me taking his place to fight.
The strength I lost is coming back little by little.
I'll show you the power
of the Perfect Clima-Tact!
You're mistaken if you think
I'm just a dainty beauty!
I can move my legs, too!
Here I come!
Thunder Charge!
Swing Arm!
That's an amazing weapon.
These are...
clouds?
There's no way I'd just lay on
the floor doing nothing, is there?
Thunderbolt... Tempo!
It's your own fault for acting so confident.
That was a surprise.
I never thought I'd be hit by lightning indoors.
What was that thing that
guarded you from the lightning?
It turned into bubbles and disappeared.
You have no chance against me
unless you solve that mystery.
I wonder if you can do it.
It was as if soap turned into bubbles.
You could be a soap human with Bubble Bubble Fruit powers.
I wonder if it's something like that.
B-But even if, for example, you figured
out what kind of powers they are,
it's not like you have a
chance to win! How insolent!
So that was right on the mark.
Now I kinda feel guilty.
You're right. My specialty is cleanliness.
I ate the Bubble Bubble Fruit...
and became a soap human
whose entire body lathers.
Isn't it wonderful?
Whoa! How sexy! To be honest,
I'd be happy to have a secretary like her.
Hey! What am I, a middle-aged guy?!
But isn't that ineffective for fighting?
It doesn't look very strong.
But I can freely manipulate the
bubbles that come out of my body.
What? What's going on?
I'll show you.
The bubbles from the bathtub are...!
Bubble Master:
Soap Sheep!
This is...
How's this? Isn't it wonderful?
You're an idiot, aren't you?
You shouldn't be deceived by my appearance.
What?
Sheep Cloud: Relaxing Bubbles!
You lost your strength at the
room's entrance. Why was that?
That's right!
That must've been her powers, too.
Bubbles!
Come to think of it, when I
stepped into this room,
there were bubbles all over the floor!
Shoot!
You noticed it too late.
My strength is fading away.
This happened earlier, too, because I
stepped on the bubbles on the floor.
You'll learn the horror of
this power little by little.
The bubbles from my body scrub away all sorts of things.
They naturally handle filth and spots, but they also sap your strength, among other things.
And I don't want you to forget that I'm
an assassin from a secret organization.
I can move my body! Her kicking
me made the bubbles go away!
I'm not gonna take this anymore!
Thunder Ball!
That weapon's power alone...
is still an unknown quantity to me.
Golden Bubbles!
What're you doing?!
I can't stand!
What?! What's wrong with my legs?!
Pretty, aren't they?
Everything I touch gains a beautiful gloss.
I'll make your skin shiny...
Every inch of your body.
A man... A man...
A man has battles that he must face head-on!
Shave!
Tempest Kick: Lotus!
Take this!
Song of the Willow!
Iron Body!
I don't know what's coming next,
so I'm gonna go ahead
and replenish my cola first.
Come to think of it, I wonder
how that deer's doing.
What the heck's going on?!
Wh-What the hell...
is this?!
That's the CP9 guy who was in the fridge!
What?! Did this monster bring him down?!
What the hell is this?
I feel like that deer was
wearing the same kind of hat.
Hey! You're not that deer-gorilla, are you?!
Hey! This can't be happening!
There's no mistake.
Kumadori-san!
He flew from the Tower of Justice?!
It can't be! Who on earth could...?
Good grief! What the hell is he?!
A voice?
Hm?
Hey, hurry up!
Why are you stopping, Nico Robin?!
Hey, are you listening, Ms. My-existence-is-a-crime?!
Hey, Lucci! Drag her along!
Grab her by her hair!
It's an order.
Get moving, Nico Robin.
Don't tell me, you still think that the
Straw Hats are coming to your rescue?
How stupid!
Are you seriously still laying your
hopes on such weak pirates?
That explosion earlier was
surely just our imagination.
There's no way that they can come here!
While you're enjoying your little dream,
we'll pass through the Gates of Justice.
The Bridge of Hesitation looms
in front of the Gates of Justice.
Underground Passage
(Current Location)
"Bridge of Hesitation
(Halfway)"
We'll cross the first half of the bridge, which is now up.
When the gates are opened,
the other half will rise from the sea,
Underground Passage
(Current Location)
"Bridge of Hesitation
(Halfway)"
and we'll finally go through
the Gates of Justice.
"Gates of Justice
(Cross-Section)"
Once the gates are closed again,
you'll never have the feeling of hope...
ever again.
The only feeling you'll have is a sense of guilt.
You'll endlessly atone for your
sin of having lived until today.
Right, Nico Robin?
Now, let's hurry.
Come on already!
Robin!
Wh-Wh-What was that?! I just heard a voice!
Hey! What was that voice?!
Chief, please take Nico Robin
and hurry on ahead.
Hm? Doors?
They don't look like iron this time.
Hm? This room is bigger. Where am I?
There you are! Pigeon guy!
I'm glad you came.